♪♪
♪ I gotta take a little time ♪
♪ A little time to
think things over ♪
♪ I better read
between the lines ♪
♪ In case I need
it when I'm older ♪
♪ Ohhhhh oh ohhhh ♪
♪ Now this mountain
I must climb ♪
♪ Feels like the world
upon my shoulders ♪
♪ Through the clouds
I see love shine ♪
♪ It keeps me warm as
life grows colder ♪
♪ In my life there's
been heartache and pain ♪
♪ I don't know if I
can face it again ♪
♪ Can't stop now, I've
traveled so far ♪
♪ To change this lonely life ♪
♪ I wanna know what love is ♪
♪ I want you to show me ♪
♪ I wanna feel what love is ♪
♪ I know you can show me ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna take
a little time ♪
♪ A little time to
look around me ♪
♪ I've got nowhere
left to hide ♪
♪ It looks like love
has finally found me ♪
♪ In my life there's
been heartache and pain ♪
♪ I don't know if I
can face it again ♪
♪ I can't stop now, I've
traveled so far ♪
♪ To change this lonely life ♪
♪ I wanna know what love is ♪
♪ I want you to show me ♪
♪ I wanna feel what love is ♪
♪ I know you can show me ♪
♪ I wanna know what love is ♪
♪ I want you to show me ♪
♪ And I wanna feel,
I wanna feel what love is ♪
♪ And I know ♪
♪ I know you can show me ♪
♪ Let's talk about love ♪
♪ I wanna know what love is ♪
♪ The love that
you feel inside ♪
♪ I want you to show me ♪
♪ And I'm feeling
so much love ♪
♪ I wanna feel what love is ♪
♪ No, you just can't hide ♪
♪ I know you can show me ♪
♪ Yeah yeah ♪
♪ I wanna know what love is ♪
♪ Let's talk about love ♪
♪ I want you to show me ♪
-♪ I wanna feel it too ♪
-♪ I wanna feel what love is ♪
♪ I wanna feel it too ♪
♪ And I know and I know,
I know you can show me ♪
♪ Show me love is real, yeah ♪
♪ I wanna know what love is ♪
♪ I wanna know ♪
♪ I want you to show me ♪
♪ I wanna know, I wanna
know, I wanna know ♪
♪ I wanna feel what love is ♪
♪ Oh, I wanna feel ♪
♪ I know you can show me ♪